So, in order to access Jotbot, I open Google and I search for Jotbot AI.
And as you see, I can see my Jotbot.com, it says Jotbot AI Writing Assistant, right?
So, I click on it and as you see, the main focus of this tool is on being your writing assistant.
So, when it comes to writing, it can help us a lot.
So, it says writing and research without the busy work, Jotbot handles the struggle of finding the right words
and sources so you can focus on your ideas, right?
So, this is basically it. So, you give it ideas and what it will give you back is the right words, you know?
So, it has this start writing option over here, as you see, it says it's free and loved by plus 1 million people, right?
And over here, as you see, we can see a pretty simple website, so it also has its use cases written over here.
So, we can use it for essay writing for source finding and outline generating, right?
And that's all.